one of the ideas that already exists but
I like it and it needs to make better
because kind of felt so great the
website and the system is a free online
trading group so if you have something
you want to give away for free offering
it and having it done in a way that it's
searchable those people who need it also
have things that are like a call-out for
hey my school class is collecting that
are called the bread fasteners on the
bread bags could you save we're
collecting UPC is from Cheerios could
you save them and so using create less
waste and make more use of the odds and
ends of ways that we do create you know
kindergarten class needs a bunch of
toilet paper rolls one block is here the
toilet paper rolls for a week that's
less toughening in the garbage and more
stuff in and remotes get the busy
streets just started so that was Apple
number 99